Very unfortunate.
매우 불행한 일입니다.
Gao Tianyang.
가오텐양.
I have no intention of saving you.
나는 당신을 구할 생각이 없습니다.
Tony!
토니!
look.
바라보다.
if you kill me
당신이 나를 죽이면
My sister definitely...
언니는 분명...
More won't help you.
더 이상 도움이 되지 않습니다.
That's it.
그게 다야.
Let me talk to my brother.
내 동생과 얘기 좀 해보자.
I'll talk to him.
내가 그 사람이랑 얘기해볼게.
it depends
때에 따라 다르지
Is there any chance.
기회가 있습니까?
lucky.
운이 좋은.
Remember that feeling.
그 느낌을 기억하세요.
This is fear.
이것은 두려움입니다.
I'll find a way to get it back.
돌려받을 수 있는 방법을 찾아보겠습니다.
I will wait.
나는 기다릴 것이다.
elder sister.
언니.
Gao Tianyang.
가오텐양.
If I die like this
내가 이대로 죽으면
Isn't this a bit unfair?
이건 좀 불공평하지 않나요?
That's it.
그게 다야.
if i should die
내가 죽어야 한다면
remember.
기억하다.
Take good care of Teacher Huang.
황선생님을 잘 보살펴주세요.
Don't worry.
괜찮아요.
You won't die.
당신은 죽지 않을 것입니다.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
elder sister.
언니.
Gao Tianyang.
가오텐양.
Have you ever thought about it?
그것에 대해 생각해 본 적이 있나요?
you must guarantee
당신은 보장해야합니다
Huang Zicheng's safety.
황쯔청의 안전.
certainly.
틀림없이.
I can't do this alone.
나 혼자서는 이 일을 할 수 없어요.
I need your cooperation.
여러분의 협조가 필요합니다.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
I will tell you.
난 당신을 말할 것이다.
There isn't much time left.
시간이 많이 남지 않았습니다.
quickly.
빠르게.
I know.
알아요.
Not to taste.
맛이 없습니다.
I changed it to another one.
다른걸로 바꿨어요
The food is delicious.
음식이 맛있다.
I just...
난 그냥...
No appetite today.
오늘은 식욕이 없습니다.
I just want to drink.
난 그냥 마시고 싶어.
According to my intuition,
내 직감에 따르면,
This should be a family affair.
이것은 가족의 일이어야 합니다.
Is a woman's intuition really so accurate?
여자의 직감이 정말 그렇게 정확할까요?
You are a public servant.
당신은 공무원입니다.
at work,
직장에서,
There won’t be too many problems.
문제가 별로 없을 겁니다.
Heartbroken.
상심했습니다.
Not really.
설마.
The only thing that worries you is your family.
당신을 걱정하는 유일한 것은 당신의 가족입니다.
And most likely
그리고 아마도
It's your sister.
네 여동생이야.
Very thorough analysis.
매우 철저한 분석.
Good logical thinking.
논리적 사고가 좋습니다.
I am right.
내가 옳다.
correct.
옳은.
In fact, you only told me,
사실 나한테만 말했잖아.
There is a younger brother and sister.
남동생과 여동생이 있습니다.
Another family?
또 다른 가족?
who knows.
누가 알아.
He's been in some trouble lately.
그 사람은 최근에 좀 곤란한 상황에 빠졌어요.
He needs my help.
그 사람은 내 도움이 필요해요.
Isn't that what life is like?
인생도 그런 것이 아닌가?
Birth, old age, illness and death, life is not eternal.
태어나고 늙고 병들고 죽고, 삶은 영원하지 않습니다.
Trouble will not escape you.
문제는 당신을 탈출하지 못할 것입니다.
Who told you they were his family?
누가 그의 가족이라고 말했습니까?
if you really do it
정말 그렇게 한다면
I have to pay.
나는 지불해야한다.
I do not know what you mean
난 당신이 무슨 뜻인지 모르겠어요
but...
하지만...
If there is still a chance to redeem it
아직 상환할 기회가 있다면
Then do it.
그럼 그렇게 하세요.
Family and friends,
가족과 친구들,
Owe each other.
서로에게 빚을 졌습니다.
Pay each other money.
서로 돈을 지불하십시오.
visible
보이는
You have a good relationship.
당신은 좋은 관계를 가지고 있습니다.
You absolutely cannot let go.
절대로 놓을 수 없습니다.
You didn't even ask me,
넌 나한테 물어보지도 않았잖아
What fees should I pay?
어떤 수수료를 지불해야 합니까?
Can I kill or burn?
죽이거나 태울 수 있나요?
What if it was murder and arson?
살인과 방화라면 어떨까요?
What happened to my hair?
내 머리카락은 어떻게 됐나요?
There is a white spot.
흰 반점이 있습니다.
Like being hit with flour.
밀가루 맞은 것처럼요.
you don't like others
넌 다른 사람을 좋아하지 않아
Touch your hair?
머리를 만져볼까?
No.
아니요.
I'm just not used to it.
나는 그것에 익숙하지 않습니다.
[Or because I killed him and burned him. ]
[아니면 내가 그를 죽이고 불태워버렸기 때문이겠지요. ]
I'm surprised.
놀랐어요.
You wouldn't do anything like that.
당신은 그런 짓을하지 않을 것입니다.
is this real?
이거 진짜야?
enough.
충분한.
let's go.
갑시다.
Kill and burn them.
그들을 죽이고 불태워라.
Pay.
지불하다.
Did you poison him?
당신이 그를 독살했나요?
You can try it yourself.
직접 시도해 볼 수 있습니다.
This wine...
이 와인은...
Not very interesting.
그다지 흥미롭지 않습니다.
Your mentality is not bad.
당신의 멘탈은 나쁘지 않습니다.
and voters.
그리고 유권자.
What else can I do?
또 무엇을 할 수 있나요?
Make you tremble with fear.
두려움에 떨게 만드십시오.
if you knew
당신이 알고 있었다면
your current situation,
당신의 현재 상황,
Things won't be that easy.
상황이 그리 쉽지는 않을 것입니다.
What exactly do you want to do?
정확히 무엇을 하고 싶으신가요?
We can talk.
우리는 이야기 할 수.
if i could decide
내가 결정할 수 있다면
I will go straight
나는 똑바로 갈 것이다
Throw you into the sea and let the fish eat you.
너를 바다에 던져 물고기가 너를 먹게 하라.
impossible.
불가능한.
At least me too
적어도 나도 마찬가지야
For you.
당신을 위한.
now this is your destiny
이제 이것이 네 운명이다
Not in my hands,
내 손에 있지 않고,
Nor is it in your hands.
그것은 당신의 손에도 없습니다.
It's in your sister's hand.
그건 언니 손에 있어요.
You guys are trying to take advantage of me.
너희들은 나를 이용하려고 한다.
To threaten my brother.
동생을 협박하려고요.
if he refuses
만약 그가 거절한다면
I'll get rid of you.
나는 당신을 제거합니다.
do not blame me.
저를 비난하지 않는다.
what are you looking for?
무엇을 찾고 계신가요?
My brother is Guo An.
내 동생은 궈안(Guo An)이다.
He can't possibly work for you.
그는 당신을 위해 일할 수 없습니다.
You are the wrong person.
당신은 잘못된 사람입니다.
is this real?
이거 진짜야?
If so, please enjoy
그렇다면 즐겨주세요
Your last 24 hours.
지난 24시간.
If that's the case I'm ok
그렇다면 난 괜찮아
Keep working for you.
당신을 위해 계속 일하세요.
Now is the panic.
지금은 공황 상태입니다.
In fact, I am still very optimistic about you.
사실, 나는 아직도 당신에 대해 매우 낙관적입니다.
You are a talented spy.
당신은 재능 있는 스파이입니다.
this is only...
이건 단지...
Just...just what?
그냥...그냥 뭐?
I thought you cared about everything.
나는 당신이 모든 것에 관심을 갖고 있다고 생각했습니다.
But it's actually you
하지만 사실은 너야
Don't care about anything.
아무것도 신경 쓰지 마세요.
You don't care about your father.
당신은 아버지에 대해 관심이 없습니다.
atau Yao Yao.
아타우 야오야오.
you don't even care
넌 신경도 안 써
your own life.
당신 자신의 삶.
You are wrong.
당신은 잘못.
I care about them too much.
나는 그들에게 너무 많은 관심을 가지고 있습니다.
I really want to protect them.
나는 정말로 그들을 보호하고 싶다.
certainly.
틀림없이.
I also have to protect myself.
나도 내 자신을 보호해야 해요.
I don't want to die and I don't want to go to jail.
나는 죽고 싶지도 않고 감옥에 가고 싶지도 않습니다.
But you keep asking me to be a spy.
그런데 당신은 계속 나에게 스파이가 되어 달라고 요구하고 있어요.
what can I do?
어떡해?
Let's make it like this.
이렇게 만들어 보겠습니다.
give me back.
나 한테 다시 돌려줘.
So this question,
그래서 이 질문은,
Let's forget about it.
그것에 대해 잊어 버리자.
I will continue to work for you.
나는 계속해서 당신을 위해 일할 것입니다.
Your honor is gone.
당신의 명예는 사라졌습니다.
After eating this,
이거 먹고 나면
Don't know what to eat next
다음에 무엇을 먹을지 모르겠어요
Still food or no food.
아직도 음식이 있거나 음식이 없습니다.
Come on, let's have a drink.
자, 한잔 하자.
Jia Tianyang.
지아 텐양.
Why did you come?
왜 왔나요?
I can't stay at home.
나는 집에 있을 수 없다.
Drink alcoholic beverages.
알코올 음료를 마시십시오.
a little.
조금.
Come in.
올.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Played by Tony
토니가 연기한
You have agreed.
당신은 동의했습니다.
Do you know what he asked?
그가 무엇을 물었는지 아시나요?
No.
아니요.
He told me to kill people.
사람을 죽이라고 하더군요.
in this case...
이 경우에는...
Do you want to do it?
하고 싶나요?
if i leave
내가 떠나면
I probably won't go back.
나는 아마 돌아 가지 않을 것이다.
Do you think I should go?
내가 가야 할 것 같아?
I have no idea.
나는 모른다.
Zicheng once told me,
Zicheng은 언젠가 나에게 이렇게 말했습니다.
He said you are a family
그는 당신이 가족이라고 말했습니다
Also a good friend.
또한 좋은 친구입니다.
It’s each other’s support.
서로의 응원입니다.
He said,
그는 말했다,
If something happens to you one day,
어느 날 당신에게 무슨 일이 생기면,
He could sacrifice himself to save you.
그는 당신을 구하기 위해 자신을 희생할 수도 있습니다.
Was he wrong?
그가 틀렸나요?
No.
아니요.
In fact, he always has been
사실 그 사람은 늘 그랬어요.
As brothers and sisters.
형제 자매로서.
He said you and him
그 사람이 말했지 너랑 그 사람이랑
And Uncle Huang.
그리고 황 삼촌.
It's family
가족이에요
and three men.
그리고 세 남자.
After returning to Macau,
마카오로 돌아온 후,
Uncle Huang is in danger.
황 삼촌이 위험에 빠졌습니다.
No matter what happens to Zi Sheng,
Zi Sheng에게 무슨 일이 일어나더라도,
To save him.
그를 구하기 위해.
But now he is in danger.
하지만 지금 그는 위험에 빠졌습니다.
Only you can save him.
오직 당신만이 그를 구할 수 있습니다.
did he ever tell you
그 사람이 너한테 말한 적 있어?
Why are you at home?
왜 집에 있어요?
Are there just the three of us left?
이제 우리 셋만 남았나요?
No.
아니요.
Yeah.
응.
Mother
어머니
Where are you?
어디세요?
Bibi.
비비.
Where are my parents?
내 부모님은 어디에 계시나요?
Tianyang.
천양.
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Where are my parents?
내 부모님은 어디에 계시나요?
I must find them.
꼭 찾아야 해요.
Your parents are both very nice.
부모님 두 분 다 정말 좋으세요.
Come out with me. quickly.
나와 함께 나오세요. 빠르게.
I want to find them.
나는 그들을 찾고 싶다.
let's go.
갑시다.
Auntie, are you okay?
아줌마, 괜찮아?
It doesn't matter.
그것은 중요하지 않습니다.
listen to me.
내 말을 들어보세요.
Come out with me quickly.
빨리 나랑 같이 나가자
But I have to find them.
하지만 난 그들을 찾아야 해요.
Tianyang.
천양.
Come out with me.
나와 함께 나오세요.
Tianyang, who let you in?
천양아, 누가 들여보내줬어?
Who asked you to come up?
누가 올라오라고 했나?
Honey.
꿀.
I must find them.
꼭 찾아야 해요.
Come out with me.
나와 함께 나오세요.
I want to find them.
나는 그들을 찾고 싶다.
Tianyang, come out, come out.
천양, 나와라, 나와라.
You take the children out first.
아이들을 먼저 데리고 나가세요.
I'll go find them.
내가 가서 찾아볼게.
No.
아니요.
I must find them.
꼭 찾아야 해요.
Why did you go up there?
거기 왜 올라갔어?
Do you want to die?
죽고 싶나요?
But I have to find them.
하지만 난 그들을 찾아야 해요.
Honey.
꿀.
I do not want to go.
나는 가고 싶지 않아.
quickly.
빠르게.
My parents are inside.
부모님은 안에 계십니다.
Please accept my condolences.
삼가 조의를 표합니다.
sun.
해.
Ayo.
아요.
Let's go home.
집에 가자.
Uncle will cook for you.
삼촌이 요리해 줄 거예요.
your parents
부모님
And your aunt.
그리고 이모.
they must see
그들은 꼭 봐야 해
The way you are now.
지금 당신의 모습.
They also grieve.
그들도 슬퍼합니다.
You still have me.
당신은 아직 나를 가지고 있습니다.
And your sister.
그리고 네 여동생.
Later the three of us
나중에 우리 셋이서
It's a family.
가족이에요.
Mari, Zisheng, mari.
마리, 자성, 마리.
Soon, both of you
곧 너희 둘 다
He is my biological son.
그는 나의 친아들입니다.
We will be brother and sister from now on.
우리는 이제부터 남매가 될 것입니다.
You have the toys I have.
당신은 내가 가지고 있는 장난감을 가지고 있습니다.
I will protect you.
내가 너를 지켜줄 께.
so,
그래서,
Ibu Zisheng
이부 쯔셩
There is a chance to escape.
탈출할 기회가 있습니다.
In order to save my parents...
부모님을 구하기 위해..
they always
그들은 항상
Treat me like family.
나를 가족처럼 대해주세요.
Never mentioned this
이 내용을 언급한 적이 없습니다.
in front of me
내 앞에
In that case, you will definitely save Zicheng.
그렇다면 당신은 반드시 Zicheng을 구하게 될 것입니다.
correct?
옳은?
I need to think of a way
방법을 생각해봐야겠어
In addition to being able to save Huang Zisheng,
황자성(Huang Zisheng)을 구할 수 있을 뿐만 아니라,
It can also be safe.
안전할 수도 있습니다.
It's too late now.
지금은 너무 늦었어요.
go to bed early.
일찍 잠자리에.
Can I
내가 할 수 있을까?
On this couch?
이 소파에?
As for me, I don’t dare to be alone.
저는 감히 혼자 있을 수가 없어요.
Home alone.
혼자 집에.
Zisheng.
Zisheng.
Zicheng, get up quickly.
Zicheng, 빨리 일어나.
Yao Yao.
야오야오.
Why did you come?
왜 왔나요?
Sister Tianyang and Tony
텐양 자매와 토니
Negotiate above.
위에서 협상하세요.
Taking advantage of this time,
이 시간을 활용하여,
Come with me.
날 따라와.
quickly.
빠르게.
hurry up.
서둘러요.
what's the situation?
상황은 어떻습니까?
All indicators are very good.
모든 지표는 매우 좋습니다.
When will he wake up?
그 사람은 언제 일어날까요?
soon.
곧.
Thanks.
감사해요.
Xiao Yi's condition has stabilized.
샤오이의 상태는 안정되었습니다.
The doctor said he would wake up soon.
의사는 그가 곧 깨어날 것이라고 말했습니다.
That's very good.
아주 좋습니다.
the information he got
그 사람이 얻은 정보
It played a big role in promoting this case.
이 사건을 홍보하는데 큰 역할을 했습니다.
Xiao Yi has a close relationship with his husband Zhang.
Xiao Yi는 남편 Zhang과 긴밀한 관계를 유지하고 있습니다.
we have to find a way
우리는 방법을 찾아야 해
Lock Boss Zhang through him.
그를 통해 장 보스를 잠그십시오.
OK
좋아요
Shen.
쉔.
SMA。
SMA。
You print the form
양식을 인쇄합니다.
for me.
나를 위한.
SMA。
SMA。
I happen to have one.
나는 우연히 하나를 가지고 있습니다.
You take it first.
당신이 먼저 가져가세요.
Thank you so much.
매우 감사합니다.
How is Huang Zisheng doing recently?
황쯔셩은 최근 어떻게 지내고 있나요?
He's fine.
그는 괜찮아.
Condition is very good.
상태는 매우 좋습니다.
it is noon now.
지금은 정오입니다.
Let's eat together.
같이 먹자.
I still have things to do at home.
아직 집에 할 일이 남아 있어요.
I dont go.
나는 가지 않는다.
you
너
Have you had any questions lately?
최근에 질문이 있으신가요?
No.
아니요.
Maybe I'm a little tired lately.
어쩌면 요즘 좀 피곤한 것 같아요.
we are still friends.
우리는 여전히 친구입니다.
what is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
if you
만약 너라면
Faced with difficult problems,
어려운 문제에 직면하여,
You can talk to me.
당신은 나에게 얘기할 수 있습니다.
I am fine.
괜찮아요.
Emotions can also be an issue.
감정도 문제가 될 수 있습니다.
What if I could help you?
내가 당신을 도울 수 있다면 어떨까요?
You think too much.
당신은 너무 많이 생각합니다.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
OK
좋아요
It would be nice if it was okay.
괜찮다면 좋을 텐데.
I'm leaving now, see you later.
지금 갈 테니 나중에 봐요.
Tuan Gao.
투안 가오.
Xiao Yi will wake up soon.
Xiao Yi는 곧 깨어날 것입니다.
You must hurry.
서둘러야 합니다.
I can't do it alone.
혼자서는 할 수 없어요.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
I need help.
도움이 필요해요.
help?
돕다?
He will do it.
그는 그것을 할 것입니다.
I will help him.
나는 그를 도울 것이다.
This is unrealistic.
이것은 비현실적입니다.
If you can find someone else,
다른 사람을 찾을 수 있다면,
I won't go to you.
나는 당신에게 가지 않을 것입니다.
Care is rigorous.
케어가 철저합니다.
I'll do it myself.
내가 직접 할게.
It's hard to escape suspicion.
의심을 피하기는 어렵습니다.
In order to save Huang Zisheng,
황자성을 구하기 위해
I was arrested.
나는 체포됐다.
this
이것
Makes no sense to me.
나에게는 이해가 되지 않습니다.
Of course, you can refuse.
물론 거절할 수 있습니다.
Xiao Yi may wake up at any time.
Xiao Yi는 언제든지 깨어날 수 있습니다.
wake up.
깨우다.
you are working hard
당신은 열심히 일하고 있습니다
Get rid of it.
그것을 제거.
He must know a lot.
그는 많은 것을 알고 있을 것입니다.
Are you threatening me?
나를 협박하는 겁니까?
No.
아니요.
I remind you.
나는 당신에게 상기시켜줍니다.
Instead of wasting time,
시간을 낭비하는 대신,
Get well soon
쾌유를 빌어요
We achieved our goal.
우리는 목표를 달성했습니다.
Who do you think I should send?
내가 누구를 보내야 한다고 생각하세요?
Who wants Xiao Yi to die most?
Xiao Yi가 가장 죽기를 원하는 사람은 누구입니까?
You just send him.
당신은 그를 보내면 됩니다.
Boss Zhang.
장 사장님.
You want me to send Mr. Zhang?
제가 장 선생님을 보내길 원하시나요?
This is better.
이게 낫다.
This is unrealistic.
이것은 비현실적입니다.
It’s impossible for Boss Zhang
장보스에게는 불가능하다
cooperation with you.
당신과의 협력.
I think this requirement is difficult to achieve.
이 요구 사항은 달성하기 어렵다고 생각합니다.
Who do you think can?
누가 할 수 있을 것 같나요?
Yao Yao.
야오야오.
Such a heavy task,
이렇게 무거운 일을,
kepada Yao Yao.
케파다 야오야오.
This is so childish.
이건 너무 유치해요.
Yao Yao received short-term training.
야오야오는 단기 훈련을 받았다.
He's not as weak as you think.
그 사람은 당신이 생각하는 것만큼 약하지 않아요.
and your help,
그리고 당신의 도움,
I believe he can solve it.
나는 그가 그것을 해결할 수 있다고 믿습니다.
Do you want to kill someone?
누군가를 죽이고 싶나요?
I will convince him.
나는 그를 설득할 것이다.
Yao Yao.
야오야오.
Boss Zhang suggested
장보스가 제안한
I was rejected.
나는 거절당했습니다.
So, he proposed to Yaoyao.
그래서 그는 Yaoyao에게 제안했습니다.
If Mr. Zhang appeared,
만일 Mr. 장씨가 등장했다.
Subject to change.
변경될 수 있습니다.
Use Boss Zhang
장보스를 이용하세요
and Boss Zhang.
그리고 장보스.
There is such a possibility.
그런 가능성이 있습니다.
So, I proposed to Yaoyao.
그래서 야오야오에게 프로포즈했어요.
He is a chess piece
그는 체스말이다
We can throw it away at any time.
우리는 언제든지 그것을 버릴 수 있습니다.
Actually, this is not bad.
실제로 이것은 나쁘지 않습니다.
can take advantage of this opportunity
이 기회를 활용할 수 있습니다
Come to test Yaoyao.
Yaoyao를 테스트하러 오세요.
If he really kills someone
그 사람이 정말 사람을 죽였다면
Can be used later.
나중에 사용할 수 있습니다.
understand.
이해하다.
Halo?
후광?
This is me.
나야.
Aura.
영기.
Gao Tianyang has already agreed.
Gao Tianyang은 이미 동의했습니다.
If so, my job is done.
그렇다면 내 일은 끝난 것이다.
not yet.
아직 아님.
You have to continue to help him
계속해서 그를 도와야 해
mission accomplished.
임무 완수.
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Gao Tianyang can't do it alone.
Gao Tianyang은 혼자서는 할 수 없습니다.
I don't believe him either.
나도 그를 믿지 않습니다.
I'm calmer
나는 더 차분하다
I...
나...
You asked me to help him kill people.
당신은 그가 사람을 죽이는 것을 도와달라고 나에게 요청했습니다.
I can not do it.
나는 그것을 할 수 없습니다.
Gao Tianyang tells you
Gao Tianyang이 알려줍니다.
What is he doing.
그는 무엇을 하고 있나요?
You just have to listen to him.
당신은 그의 말을 듣기만 하면 됩니다.
Work it out with him.
그와 함께 해결해보세요.
this...
이것...
This is not the case.
그렇지 않다.
How could I kill someone?
어떻게 사람을 죽일 수 있습니까?
Everything exists for the first time.
모든 것은 처음으로 존재합니다.
The target has fainted.
대상이 기절했습니다.
Kill someone.
누군가를 죽여라.
Who can't fight.
싸우지 못하는 사람.
That's easy.
그건 쉽습니다.
This important thing,
이 중요한 것,
if i fail,
내가 실패하면,
Killing someone in front of Guo An,
궈안 앞에서 사람을 죽이고,
They won't let me go.
그들은 나를 놓아주지 않을 것입니다.
I believe in your ability.
나는 당신의 능력을 믿습니다.
There is also Gao Tianyang's ability.
Gao Tianyang의 능력도 있습니다.
think about it.
그것에 대해 생각해보세요.
If you work together to solve it
함께 해결해 나가면
This mission,
이번 미션은,
Will he let you get caught?
그가 당신을 붙잡도록 놔둘까요?
He will protect you.
그분은 당신을 보호하실 것입니다.
What if it fails?
실패하면 어떻게 되나요?
It can only succeed.
성공할 수 밖에 없습니다.
This is the only hope
이것이 유일한 희망이다
You and Huang Zisheng.
당신과 황쯔셩.
I can't risk my life.
나는 내 생명을 위험에 빠뜨릴 수 없습니다.
Think of your sister.
당신의 여동생을 생각해보세요.
dan Huang Zisheng.
단 황쯔셩(Huang Zisheng).
You are not for yourself,
당신은 자신을 위한 것이 아닙니다.
You do it for yourself too.
당신도 스스로를 위해 그것을합니다.
No.
아니요.
Huang Zisheng mati.
황쯔성마티.
Gao Tianyang captured the first person
Gao Tianyang이 첫 번째 사람을 포착했습니다.
It's you.
당신이에요.
Do.
하다.
Not only did you save them;
당신은 그들을 구했을 뿐만 아니라;
you will also get
너도 얻을 것이다
Lots of gifts.
많은 선물.
after that,
이후,
Master Yu will let you leave Jinhai.
유 선생님께서 진하이를 떠나도록 허락하실 것입니다.
Where is my sister?
내 여동생은 어디에 있나요?
Are you going to let go?
놓아주실 건가요?
We start negotiating.
우리는 협상을 시작합니다.
This means you agree.
이는 귀하가 동의한다는 의미입니다.
I don't want my sister
나는 내 여동생을 원하지 않아요
Something happened to my sister.
내 여동생에게 무슨 일이 일어났어요.
I hope he returns safely.
그가 무사히 돌아오길 바랍니다.
Is it possible?
가능합니까?
of.
의.
As long as you do well,
당신이 잘하는 한,
You can get
당신은 얻을 수 있습니다
The treatment you want.
원하시는 진료입니다.
what should I do?
어떻게 해야 합니까?
I've never killed anyone.
나는 누구도 죽인 적이 없습니다.
I've never done that either.
나도 그런 적 없어.
Managed by others.
다른 사람이 관리합니다.
There is no other choice.
다른 옵션은 없습니다.
but i really don't want to
하지만 난 정말 그러고 싶지 않아
Become someone else's pawn again.
다시 다른 사람의 전당포가 되십시오.
Days like this,
이런 날,
I'm done.
난 끝났어.
They gave me earrings.
그들은 나에게 귀걸이를 주었다.
tell me 24 hours
24시간 말해줘
24 hours.
24 시간.
to understand
이해하다
our situation.
우리 상황.
Where are the earrings?
귀걸이는 어디에 있나요?
I left it at home.
집에 두고 왔습니다.
I went out secretly to look for you.
나는 당신을 찾으러 몰래 나갔습니다.
Jia Tianyang.
지아 텐양.
I just couldn't sink any deeper.
나는 더 이상 깊이 가라앉을 수가 없었다.
They told me to kill people.
사람들을 죽이라고 하더군요.
no matter what happens,
무슨 일이 일어나더라도,
There's no way I can do it.
내가 할 수 있는 방법은 없어요.
If you don't do this,
이렇게 하지 않으면
They won't let you go.
그들은 당신을 놓아주지 않을 것입니다.
He won't let Zicheng go either.
그는 Zicheng도 놓아주지 않을 것입니다.
Although,
하지만,
You cannot kill.
당신은 죽일 수 없습니다.
This is my limit.
이게 내 한계 야.
law?
법?
You pulled Huang Zisheng into the water,
당신은 황쯔셩(Huang Zisheng)을 물 속으로 끌어당겼고,
Lure him onto the ship.
그를 배로 유인하세요.
and become hostages.
그리고 인질이 됩니다.
Where are your limits?
당신의 한계는 어디입니까?
where to?
어디로?
sorry.
죄송합니다.
I know what I said.
나는 내가 무슨 말을 했는지 안다.
It's too late.
너무 늦었어요.
but i can't
하지만 난 못해
Drag you into the water.
당신을 물 속으로 끌고 가세요.
Because you are
왜냐하면 당신은
Our only hope.
우리의 유일한 희망.
You don't need to tell me this.
나에게 이것을 말할 필요는 없습니다.
Doesn't matter.
상관없어요.
Jia Tianyang.
지아 텐양.
You must have a way, right?
분명 방법이 있을 거예요, 그렇죠?
Zisheng once said:
Zisheng은 다음과 같이 말한 적이 있습니다.
You want to help us break free.
당신은 우리가 자유롭게 될 수 있도록 돕고 싶어합니다.
no one will choose
아무도 선택하지 않을 거야
Choose to escape,
탈출을 선택하고,
Still have to continue sinking.
그래도 계속 가라앉아야 합니다.
How can I trust you?
내가 너를 어떻게 믿어?
if i want to lie to you
내가 너에게 거짓말을 하고 싶다면
I can
저 할 수 있어요
Wear earrings when going out.
외출 시 귀걸이를 착용하세요.
Let them listen to our conversation.
그들이 우리 대화를 듣게 해주세요.
If you don't believe in my ability
내 능력을 믿지 못한다면
I can assure you,
나는 당신에게 확신할 수 있습니다.
I will definitely become better
나는 반드시 나아질 것이다
dari Huang Zisheng.
황자성(Huang Zisheng).
because i have experienced
내가 경험했기 때문에
There are even crueler moments than that.
그보다 더 잔인한 순간도 있다.
No one rescued me at that time.
그 당시에는 나를 구해준 사람이 아무도 없었습니다.
The prison here is very scary.
여기 감옥은 정말 무섭습니다.
You already feel it.
당신은 이미 그것을 느끼고 있습니다.
No one can save you now.
이제 누구도 당신을 구할 수 없습니다.
just me.
나만.
help me.
도와주세요.
I beg you.
부탁드립니다.
Will you help us?
우리를 도와주실 건가요?
I can not.
나는 할 수 없다.
I met your sister.
나는 당신의 여동생을 만났습니다.
He's the only family you have, right?
그 사람이 당신의 유일한 가족이죠, 그렇죠?
If something goes wrong,
뭔가 잘못되면,
Everything points to me.
모든 것이 나를 가리킨다.
I beg you.
부탁드립니다.
Don't hurt my family.
내 가족에게 상처를 주지 마세요.
please.
제발.
Can you do it well?
잘 할 수 있나요?
of.
의.
I can.
저 할 수 있어요.
Welcome to the special forces game.
특수 부대 게임에 오신 것을 환영합니다.
I don't want to kill anyone.
나는 누구도 죽이고 싶지 않습니다.
You must learn to protect yourself.
당신은 자신을 보호하는 법을 배워야합니다.
It will save your life at important moments.
중요한 순간에 당신의 생명을 구할 것입니다.
Physical training.
신체 훈련.
It is a basic guarantee
기본보증입니다
mission accomplished.
임무 완수.
I couldn't wake up.
나는 깨어날 수 없었다.
stop.
멈추다.
Remove the protector.
보호 장치를 제거하십시오.
Actual combat
실제 전투
No protection.
보호가 없습니다.
wake up.
깨우다.
stop.
멈추다.
You can have dinner today.
오늘 저녁을 먹어도 돼요.
Your task is simple.
귀하의 작업은 간단합니다.
Continue the game.
게임을 계속하세요.
mission accomplished.
임무 완수.
Win a lot of bonuses.
많은 보너스를 받으세요.
target value
목표치
Maybe it's your mission goal.
어쩌면 그것이 당신의 임무 목표일 수도 있습니다.
Maybe your partner too.
어쩌면 당신의 파트너도 마찬가지일 것입니다.
any problem?
무슨 문제라도 있어?
Why did you choose me?
왜 나를 선택했어요?
Because your skills are very good.
실력이 아주 좋으니까.
I'm always keeping an eye on you.
나는 항상 당신을 지켜보고 있습니다.
All those who love special forces games,
특수부대 게임을 좋아하시는 모든 분들,
You must have a special forces dream.
특수부대 꿈이 있으실 텐데요.
Let me help you solve it.
문제를 해결하도록 도와드리겠습니다.
how much longer?
얼마나 더?
I wanted to leave before the game started.
경기 시작 전에 떠나고 싶었어요.
You should be jailed.
당신은 투옥되어야합니다.
It's just a job.
그것은 단지 직업일 뿐입니다.
Believe me.
나를 믿어.
You will be attracted to him.
당신은 그에게 매력을 느낄 것입니다.
It's good for you and your family
그것은 당신과 당신의 가족에게 좋습니다
Live well.
잘 살다.
You always hide your abilities.
당신은 항상 자신의 능력을 숨깁니다.
I want him to believe
나는 그가 믿기를 바란다
I am
그래요
Same player as him.
그와 같은 선수.
if you say so
당신이 그렇게 말한다면
I already know.
나는 이미 알고 있다.
from now on,
지금부터,
All actions are subject to my direction.
모든 행동은 나의 지시에 따릅니다.
OK
좋아요
I will listen to you.
나는 당신의 말을 듣습니다.
Are we
우리는
No need to kill?
죽일 필요는 없지?
certainly.
틀림없이.
we will kill
우리는 죽일 것이다
Who can't wake up.
깨어나지 못하는 사람.
Even if you don't kill him
그 사람을 죽이지 않더라도
He will die too.
그도 죽을 것이다.
If you think so,
네가 그렇게 생각한다면,
You'll feel better.
기분이 좋아질 거예요.
But he is still alive.
하지만 그는 아직 살아있습니다.
I'm not as great as you think.
나는 당신이 생각하는 것만큼 대단한 사람이 아닙니다.
Now we have two options.
이제 우리에게는 두 가지 옵션이 있습니다.
First.
첫 번째.
Join me.
같이 해.
And killed him silently.
그리고 조용히 그를 죽였습니다.
Other options?
다른 옵션?
You can't kill him.
당신은 그를 죽일 수 없습니다.
Surrender to the National Security Agency.
국가안보국(National Security Agency)에 항복하세요.
But you should go to jail.
하지만 감옥에 가야 해요.
What are your options?
당신의 선택은 무엇입니까?
Is it hard to choose?
선택하기 어렵나요?
Cooperate with me to save Huang Zisheng,
나와 협력하여 황자성(Huang Zisheng)을 구하라.
It can also save your family.
또한 가족을 구할 수도 있습니다.
I will find a way to free you.
나는 당신을 자유롭게 할 방법을 찾을 것입니다.
You're caught.
당신은 잡혔습니다.
Me too.
저도요.
I have no idea.
나는 모른다.
what do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
go home.
집에가.
go to sleep.
자러 가세요.
Starting tomorrow, we will move.
내일부터 이사를 갑니다.